The very first OLIVE YOUNG store in the US
OLIVE YOUNG
Pasadena
Sue Han / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMarketing Dept.
Saul Martinez / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USA l Century City
Kang Myung-ji / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMerchandising Dept.
Countless challenges, setbacks,
and unexpected obstacles
On a path no one had traveled before
A team of people
worked tirelessly to find the answers
The story of OLIVE YOUNG's journey into the US
— told by the people who lived it
OLIVE YOUNG
Retail Can't Cross Borders?
OLIVE YOUNG's Journey into the US
PART 1
Why Did OLIVE YOUNG
Choose the United States?
Kang Myung-ji / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMerchandising Dept.
Sue Han / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMarketing Dept.
Saul Martinez / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USA l Century City
PART 2
A Path No One Had Traveled Before
Kang Myung-ji / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMerchandising Dept.
Saul Martinez / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USA l Century City
OLIVEYOUNG Pasadena
Grand Opening Ceremony
Teresa Nicolas / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣPasadena
PART 3
Welcome to OLIVE YOUNG!
Kang Myung-ji / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMerchandising Dept.
Saul Martinez / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USA l Century City
Sue Han / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMarketing Dept.
PART 4
TEAM OLIVE YOUNG
Proven by Results
Kang Myung-ji / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USAㅣMerchandising Dept.
Saul Martinez / CJ OLIVE YOUNG USA l Century City
The opening of OLIVE YOUNG's first US store
was never the finish line
On a path where no roadmap existed
they continue to find new answers
The story of OLIVE YOUNG continues
Driven by the people bold enough
to create what comes next
Retail Can't Cross Borders?
OLIVE YOUNG's Journey into the US