Brian Thompson
CJ Foods US) Asian Cuisine,
Marketing Frozen Asian & Ethnic Team
Amy Bunch
CJ Foods US) Foodservice Marketing Mgmt
Megan Elliott
CJ Foods US) Asian Cuisine
Brand Partnership Mgmt
Rebecca Thompson
CJ Foods US) Asian Cuisine
Marketing Frozen Asian & Ethnic Mgmt
Why We Fell in Love
with K-Food
Our First Encounter
Megan Elliott
CJ Foods US
Brian Thompson
Amy Bunch
CJ Foods US
Rebecca Thompson
One of America's most popular comfort foods;
boiled macaroni tossed in rich, creamy cheese sauce
Hooked on the Spicy Flavors
of K-Food
The Effort to Bring K-Food
to America
An event featuring 12 bibigo gifts
for 2 influencers who are fans of the brand
K-Food's Challenge
in America
Bringing K-food
on the American table
As ONE TEAM
We pursue new dreams
Nick Fabel
CJ Foods US
Desiree Loberg