Opening its first store,
OLIVE YOUNG has officially entered the US market,
the world’s leading beauty trendsetter.
To mark the beginning
of this exciting new chapter,
Chairman Lee Jay Hyun visited
OLIVE YOUNG Pasadena to meet with the team.
Driven by OLIVE YOUNG’s DNA
of relentless innovation,
the mission to share the value of healthy beauty
beyond Korea and into the global market
has now begun.
In May 2026, OLIVE YOUNG’s global journey
reached a new milestone in the United States.
The opening of OLIVE YOUNG’s
first US store in Pasadena
marks its first step
into the American beauty market
and the beginning of a new mission to go global.
As a differentiated
beauty and lifestyle platform,
OLIVE YOUNG offers a completely new
beauty experience to customers in the US,
one that sets it apart from competing retailers.
From an expanded curated selection
spanning beauty to lifestyle products
to expert health and beauty routine know-how
and its signature
friendly and dynamic customer service,
OLIVE YOUNG offers a never-before-seen
comprehensive customer experience.
OLIVE YOUNG has only just taken the first step.
The expansion of its US operations,
both online and offline,
is expected to accelerate.
OLIVE YOUNG plans to build
its core presence in the West
with California as the hub,
and then gradually expand
to East and South-Central US.
Customers had looked forward
to OLIVE YOUNG’s opening so much
that a long line stretched outside.
And the Pasadena store is already providing them
with a new experience unique to OLIVE YOUNG.
During his visit to OLIVE YOUNG Pasadena,
Chairman Lee Jay Hyun offered the staff
words of encouragement
for taking the first steps
onto the global stage.
He stressed that the opening
of OLIVE YOUNG Pasadena
marks a great beginning of a quest
to the global stage.
He urged the staff to go beyond
K-beauty and K-wellness
and encourage US customers to embrace
a healthy, stylish everyday lifestyle.
OLIVE YOUNG’s new mission of bringing
true K-beauty and K-lifestyle to the US market
has already begun.
And this journey is now set to accelerate
across the global stage.