This is the first global shop.
We start from here,
then we'll go to anywhere else in the world.
OLIVE YOUNG and all of that.
I was so excited when I heard you were opening.
So it's nice to see it in person, too,
and be able to test it out.
For nearly two years,
the staff here have worked as one
to open OLIVE YOUNG Pasadena
and launch OLIVE YOUNG’s
e-commerce operations in the US.
They say at first,
there wasn’t a clear understanding
of why we had to go global.
But building a real presence in America
made them realize the scale of their achievement,
K-beauty’s stature, and the reason
for CJ Group’s vision to go global.
Truly identifying with this vision,
the staff have worked hard.
I'm so happy that we have all the options
to test everything.
We got the skin scan
and then they told us off of our results.
It is constantly cutting edge products
that we don't usually see around here,
so I'm so excited to be here.
As K-beauty continues to gain momentum
around the world and in the US,
we believe this is the perfect time to go global.
Using K-beauty as our foundation,
we’ve set our sights
on the $176 billion US beauty market.
We’re competing with major retailers
like Sephora and Ulta,
who have introduced some K-beauty brands,
but the brands they treat only number around 20.
OLIVE YOUNG is not just another K-beauty retailer;
we helped shape K-beauty into a global trend.
With our Pasadena Store
and e-commerce operations,
we are the first company to deliver
nearly 500 K-beauty brands across America.
We’ve entered the US market
aiming to not just elevate K-beauty
but also become a gamechanger
in the US beauty market.
We want to become the platform
where customers first discover
new trends and keep returning,
setting a new standard
in the US beauty retail market.
Demand is set to grow explosively.
In just the past two or three years,
the pace of the K-wave has accelerated,
whether in food, content, or beauty.
We expect K-beauty to keep rising
for at least the next five to ten years.
Let’s invest boldly and move faster.
It’s very valuable work and very new,
and all the time we keep evolving.
All the time we introduce new things,
like trendy things, and we let our customers know
what is new and what is good for them
from your sincere heart.
I respect your energy and passion.
Your work, your portion is really important.
This is, I think, our historical moment.
Why? We are not only getting
into the US market.
This is the beginning of going worldwide.
Get on our journey
to spread the K-lifestyle all over the world.
You are the frontier, I hope, with me.
Get on this beautiful future journey with me, okay?
My goal as a store manager for OLIVE YOUNG
and my commitment
is to ensure that we continue to build the culture
and the DNA of OLIVE YOUNG.
We learned so much about OLIVE YOUNG in Korea,
and I feel it's my responsibility
to continue that DNA
and the culture here in the US.
But it's my goal and my responsibility
to continue the culture and continue the DNA
through our third, our fourth,
and our hundredth store
that we have in the future.
Hello!
Welcome to OLIVE YOUNG US