It's really been a pleasure and honor
to spend the day with you.
Every day,
we have an opportunity to try our best.
we have an opportunity to show resilience.
Every day,
we have a chance to dream big again
and make it happen, right?
And I'm very thankful
for having the opportunity
to drive our Asian business.
And I would be curious to see if you have
any advice for us as a new leadership team
on things to be mindful of.
You have talent individually.
I trust it. I believe in that.
And your team was well combined.
Your competition is very good, I think.
Young, too. Energetic man.
Old, experienced man.
New, from the outside, experienced man.
And the middle.
It's well combined.
So your teamwork, your leader's teamwork,
that's very important.
Wherever we go,
we all share we must go there.
All members of your team
must share the same thing.
That's the most important.
That's what I keep saying to my people.
So you, all the time, have to talk to,
communicate with your members.
What brings me
the most joy and passion about this is
the idea of one table, one team,
and the fact that how we work together
and how we drive results
is a piece
that is what makes food service fun.
And that's the thing I love.
How do we do that and do it together?
So that's the need of how do we get folks
going in the same direction
and working on the right stuff
to be able to drive the growth we need.
There's a lot of various pieces
of the CJ world.
And one of the things
that I see the most potential in is
the opportunity to leverage the power
of the entirety of CJ
on how teams have worked together
across those businesses
to bring things together.
Of course, we have so many other areas.
But I said based on the "lifestyle."
That means people think it makes sense.
So for example, food and drama
doesn't match, people think.
But when you see in K-dramas,
they eat ramyun.
They use the OLIVE YOUNG cosmetics, right?
So it's all connected.
Like we all get together and get the synergy.
So we have very good communication globally
and with even other companies together.
Dreaming by myself is just a dream,
but dreaming together
becomes a reality, right?
When I recall my life, I kept dreaming.
I made new dreams,
made dreams come true, actually.
Like I kept making a dream higher and higher
and kept reaching for the dream.
Same thing for K-food, K-pop.
Twenty, thirty years ago,
nobody believed what I was saying.
American people, global people
will listen to our music, watch our dramas.
And a company
that truly wanted to win and own that.
And that really resonated with me.
And I wanted to be a part of that journey.
It's leading in innovation.
It's leading with insights.
It's playing offense against the competition.
And that's really what gets me excited
about the next part of this journey.
How do you think,
in terms of the total global business,
and you've referenced
a few different parts of the business,
how do you think about prioritization
of investment or growth?
I can say that a new start is first, I think.
If you choose whether new or old,
rather I choose new.
On the other hand,
almost all the time you must try new things
and prepare for the future
and prepare new things.
Whatever you have here is good,
but still you must think about the next step.
The green and growing mindset
and the sense of urgency,
what it takes to be a leader, and winning.
And so from an R&D organization,
with the innovation
and having that mindset and that spirit,
it's very encouraging for me.
I do believe we've got a team spirit
and also complementary skills
to bring forward the vision.
As I think about
capabilities and innovation specifically,
where do you see innovation going?
What types of tools or things do you think
could really help us grow?
So for a food company, processed food company,
CPG (Consumer Packaged Goods) company,
marketing is very important.
Furthermore, these days,
with a digital environment, marketing means more.
That's no doubt.
But without technology, it doesn't make sense.
That's my philosophy.
So that means a food company
needs a very strong, high technology for the food.
That's my philosophy.
And what brings you that is,
I say ONLY ONE philosophy,
and try to do new things, and trends,
not only for marketing,
but even for technology.
'What's the new technology?'
Those kind of curiosity
Those kind of curiosity is the key
to encourage yourself
and try to find new things.
That's the reason why I keep saying ONLY ONE.
Show me new, new things,
evolved things,
next things, next stage.
That's what I keep asking my people.
You know, I see a lot of really good things
from the CJ culture
and I see a lot of good things,
either Korean culture and US culture.
How do we take the best of both
and make this, you know,
kind of the powerhouse that it could be?
Also, I know it belongs to the leaders,
but how can we see that?
Both sides' pros, we should take it
and make a good, balanced-well mixture.
But it's all about the same goal.
It's like the best efficiency and best things,
we'll do the best.
As I said earlier, I represent,
I'm very humbled to
represent a big part of the overall company
and a bunch of people
who are doing an amazing job every day
and showing up and making great products
and delivering for the customer and for the consumer.
And it's really around sort of, you know,
how do you see the leadership capabilities,
the right talent profile
and what are those sort of key cultural element
that really give you confidence, that whether it be
this team or any other team in the organization,
that you look at to make sure
we're ready for this next step?
Something I was a little bit,
not surprised, rather really satisfied was
all my, using the important keywords or like
what I mentioned through the graph
was already in your mind.
Those kinds of things made me think,
'Oh, this is real potential.'
And the way you speak together,
that kind of environmental mood, I can tell.
Good attitude and the way
you're speaking together
is like eager to communicate,
eager to make something
and cooperative kind of mind or circumstance,
I can see it.
This morning, my daughter wakes up in the morning,
she's listening to K-pop.
She comes home from school, she does her schoolwork,
and then she watches K-dramas every single day.
And then she's listening to music again
as she has her Korean face mask
and Korean skincare on.
And I've been able to see this in real life
over the last six years.
And it's given me a reason to believe
that this next generation here in the United States,
and I know it's not just the United States,
it's in Europe, it's global.
So as you think out five, ten years,
what are some of your big dreams
that maybe you haven't shared with us yet?
The other vision is an abstract vision,
which is the Korean lifestyle
that's spread more globally.
People enjoy the Korean lifestyle.
That can be one of my duty
and one of my old vision
and the present vision too.
Like to Federico,
I said you must know more Korean food
and if you start to know more Korean-style life,
you might really realize new things.
So it might be very enjoyable.
Actually, you welcomed me
and I said welcome on board
on life company CJ Group.
We are not only a food company.
I all the time say we are a life company.
As you know that we are not only food
but also health and beauty
and style and convenience,
so many cultural things.
So we call that a "life company."
It's a very strong arm to win
in the food market too.
We are not only just a food company.
We are the food company with lifestyle.
That's a really good chance
because as you know,
the K-wave is kind of a huge trend
in the States and worldwide,
so you have good chance.
And also, as you must know,
our company's philosophy is,
as you might heard already, ONLY ONE.
We must do all time the first.
We must do the best.
If you are a little late,
you must differentiate.
That means in the food market,
someday you must be a No.1
and the best company
and totally different from other companies.
This is not just a dream.
I believe we can make it.
We have a chance. We have the weapons.
So we will definitely win.
I say it's a global food market,
especially K-food is like a major wave
and a major Asian category,
and we have the strongest power in that area.
Next year, you will see
that we are the company
with the highest growth rate
in the food market.
Definitely, we can achieve that goal,
and we will be.
So if we keep up
as a high growth market rate company
for five to ten years,
we're going to be a hugely different company.
Okay? You can do it, right?