We are not only getting into the US market.
This is the beginning of going worldwide.
We are not only food,
but also health, beauty, style, and convenience.
That becomes a very strong weapon
to win in the food market, too.
Because, as you know, the K-wave
is a huge trend in the States and worldwide
So I would like introduce Korean,
what we call the K-wave or K-lifestyle,
all over the world.
Korean people have a special kind of DNA like me.
Keep trying to do things and change something thing.
That's the reason why
I keep doing things like introducing
and making it as an industry.
So the base case here is we are facing
a much more uncertain and insecure world.
And therefore, prudent companies
are going to diversify supply chains,
and they're going to
diversify their export markets.
K-food is really an opportunity to
expand and enhance that experience,
complete that experience
of loving Korean culture.
if you look at many recent things from Korea
that have become popular in the United States,
part of the reason they've become popular
is people feel like they are special
by introducing them to others.
We must always be first.
We must be the best.
If you are a little late, you must differentiate.
That means in the food market,
someday we must be
the No.1 and the best company,
and totally different from other companies.
Who must achieve, must get the goal,
and that's our philosophy and my nature
and my group people's nature, right?
We have got a chance now, so we must speed up.
And we can be the No.1 in this industry, I believe.
I respect your energy and passion.
Your work, your portion is really important.
So get on our journey
to spread the K-lifestyle to all of the world.
My goal as a store manager for OLIVE YOUNG
and my commitment
is to ensure that we continue
to build the culture and the DNA of OLIVE YOUNG.
It's something that we push
and kind of collaborate with
while still aligning with their vision and scope.
More and more authentic Korean food represented,
flavor is becoming increasingly global.
And the US has been and will continue
to be even more so on the forefront of that.