Chairman Lee Jay Hyun
visited CJ 4DPLEX America,
a pioneer of a new moviegoing culture
in the world's largest film market,
to encourage employees
and share the company's vision for global growth.
Building on collaborations
with major theater chains,
CJ 4DPLEX has been expanding infrastructure
in the Americas
while advancing content development
and technological innovation
through partnerships with Hollywood Studios.
During the visit, the Chairman toured AMC's
newly opened SCREENX premium theater
and experienced its immersive viewing environment
and technological capabilities firsthand.
He also met with
renowned Hollywood producer Jerry Bruckheimer,
best known for blockbuster franchises
such as “Top Gun” and “F1: The Movie.”
Through a special screening,
the Chairman experienced
the technology firsthand
and exchanged ideas on strengthening
the competitiveness of 4DX and SCREENX.
In addition, he met with leaders
at CJ 4DPLEX America,
who are driving the company's growth
in the Americas.
With rising demand
for premium formats in the region,
he emphasized the importance
of accelerating theater expansion,
securing differentiated content,
and advancing technological capabilities
to evolve into a world-leading
immersive platform.
I think we are the game changer and leader
of worldwide exhibition business.
So I believe we're totally going to change
the exhibition business.
Leveraging the growing recognition
of its premium-format technologies
in the Americas,
CJ 4DPLEX plans to further accelerate
its global expansion.